//////////////////////////////////////////////
//////THIS SKIN REQUIERS MAGICKMETER
//////https://github.com/khanhas/MagickMeter
//////////////////////////////////////////////

I guess I could make a qucik readme.txt for who wants to read this
To change the top text, just press the first vertical half of the skin
To change the bottom text, do the opposite
You can right click it to make the text stay in the image or go offskin, 
if you want the normal right click behaivour, just press CTRL+RGHTCLCK

◘ History
I made this so I can make racist dogs memes while offline and without imgflip.com

◘ Uses
Meme maker
You can use it in a positive way or negative way

◘ Important stuff
I tried to make this scalable so that's why you might see a lot of parantheses in the .ini

doge.ini:
•You see that RS variable, it holds a lot of things, the ones you might care about are:
 -Size: This is the font size basically, which is MN (MagicNumber, default is 1000) devided by 12, 
        if you want to change it, just change 12 to a lower or higher value
 -Case: This makes all the text UPPERCASE, just remove the whole "Case Upper |" if you don't want all caps text

Variables.inc:
•This is the easy stuff to understand
 -MN: This is the Width and Height of the skin, default is 1000, you can change it to any size, the text should scale as well
 -TT: Top Text
 -DV: Bottom Text
 -PIC: This is the file of the current pic, you can change to any image you want, as an example, if you download a pic, 
       copy/cut it into the folder and change Doge.png to the filename it has (look up supported filetypes on the Rainmeter site)

◘ For professionals
You can do whatever you want fuck off

◘ Widescreen
Yes indeed, I made a widescreen version cause why the fuck now, only thing you should take note about
•Variables.inc
 -MNW and MNH: Width and Height respectivally, since I don't know and don't want to make the Height always be 79% of the Width,
               you change the size to work with the meme you need
 -MN: Arithmetic mean

◘ Known bugs that I won't fix
When you refresh the skin, the CCLT Variable dosen't change, the CCLT variable helps with cliping the skin,
to fix it just choose one of the 2 actions when you right click

◘ Usefull links
https://docs.rainmeter.net/manual/meters/image/
https://codepen.io/ckm100/pen/dPLyjZ
https://github.com/khanhas/MagickMeter/wiki/Text

◘ Shoutouts
Unofficial Discord Rainmeter Server
khanhas - for MagickMeter
Classy
Eldog - for reminding me of MagickMeter
Felix
eskimojo
MiniDev
A Normal Furry - for the automatic Magick download
Myself
who else is there...
Yeah let's give a quick shout out to Christina Applegate
*claps*